yellowpagecity.com 2018-12-31

# YellowPageCity.com - Privacy Policy

#### Our Commitment To Privacy:

Your privacy is important to us.  To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.  To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

#### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the YellowPageCity.Com website.  On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials.  The types of personal information collected at  these pages are: Name, Address, Phone, Credit Card, etc... 

#### The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete the order.  We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers.  For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of woman filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

#### Our Commitment To Data Security:

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

#### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important.  For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

#### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:

You can correct fatal errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. Add or Update Your Listing

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
